letsdraw.it 2017-09-28

# Privacy policy / Multiplayer online drawing game. Guess and draw - #LetsDrawIt

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last modified on ​15.11.2016. 

This Privacy Policy refers to https://letsdraw.it. This page informs you of our **policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information** we receive from users of the Site. 

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. 

### Information Collection And Use 

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your IP, name, email and age. 

You can use this Site **without registering.** In this case we will collect basic data like your IP or browser type. (For more information see Log Data). 

If you decide to register your email, profile photo and full name will be provided by third party as Facebook, Google, Yahoo, Microsoft, etc. 

### Drawing (catalog) policy

This Site offers an online game. In order to participate in the game you are supposed to type words and draw pictures. We store all the words and pictures in database with link to user who created them. We reserve all rights on the pictures. We will use the pictures further in game and we will publish the pictures in online catalog. 

All the words you enter and pictures you draw may be randomly used in game. Please mind that this site is also popular among underaged children and don’t write or draw rude and vulgar words (except in private rooms) 

#### Underaged users

We ought to inform you that Picture Catalog may contain words and pictures inappropriate for children due to its many authors (and not the site’s administrator) as mentioned in previous paragraph. If you are younger than 12, please inform your parents about using this site and avoid games with certain categories. 

### Ads

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated?hl=en)

Ads help this site’s administrator with operation costs. Please don’t block ads and exclude this site if you are using some kind of ad-blocker. Thank you. 

### Cookies

During the visit of the Site, small data files called cookies may be placed into the visitor’s electronic device. Their main task is to improve and simplify the usage of the websites. The Site does not use cookies for any other reasons than stated above, and may not find out personal data such as your name or email address. 

### Log Data 

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. The information collected and stored automatically is used solely for the optimization of the Portal such as measuring the number of visitors, to solve problems with the accessibility of the websites etc. 

### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

#### Changes To This Privacy Policy 

Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. 

#### Contact Us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
